Stephen Cooper

Cedar Park, TX 78613 scooper@indeed.com +1 512 689 4576

Graduate from Texas State University with a Bachelor's Degree in Medieval History, with 6+ years of work experience. Having studied in multiple countries, I have learned to be a flexible and studious problem solver. I am a clear and efficient communicator, driven innovator, and decisive forward thinker, always seeking positions of responsibility and leadership. It is my intent to excel in the face of challenge, be an active team member, and to be reliably exceptional in any given role.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Technical Apprentice Engineer

Indeed-Austin, TX February 2024 to Present

- Work to assist in the engineering needs of the DEIB+ team
- Study and become proficient in multiple diverse fields of programming

Manager

Axl Amusements Sherwood Forest Faire-McDade, TX March 2018 to Present

- Supervision of staff, including hiring, firing, & scheduling
- Trusted with full responsibility for handling and movement of cash
- Safety checks and repairs of equipment

Client Success Specialist

Indeed-Austin, TX May 2022 to February 2024

- Provide long-term support for clients via email, phone, and Zoom
- Work closely with sales teams to maintain revenue and coverage over a large book of business Mentor new team members and help to support them as they grow into the role

Client Optimization Specialist (Contractor for Indeed)

Indeed Flex-Austin, TX June 2021 to May 2022

- Provide active phone and email support to address client concerns
- Top 10% of agents in Q3 & Q4 of 2021, and Q1 & Q2 of 2022
- Train and shadow new hires
- Present best practices, workflow & efficiency tips, and helpful updates to other teams within the department

Education

Certificate in Software Engineering

General Assembly - Remote February 2024 to June 2024

Bachelor of Arts in History

TEXAS STATE UNIVERSITY San Marcos - San Marcos, TX May 2021

Associate in Arts

Austin Community College District - Austin, TX

Skills

- · Adobe Photoshop
- · Graphic Design
- Efficient & Effective Communication
- Supervising Experience
- Conflict Resolution
- Strong Focus on Innovation Proficiencies
- Microsoft Office (Excel, Power Point, Word)
- Research
- Problem Solving
- · Writing Skills
- Mentoring
- Research

Certifications and Licenses

Software Engineering Certificate - General Assembly

June 2024 to Present

Software Engineering Bootcamp with Java and React | 448 hours

Issue Date: 6/13/2024

Course Start Date: 2/12/2024

Date of Completion: 5/31/2024